since its establishment in 1848 in
london
prudential group has now became one of
the world's leading financial group
with more than 24 million customers and
counting
across the globe particularly in the
united kingdom
usa and in asia prudential vietnam is a
proud member of the prudential group
the world's leading financial
institution with an outstanding
reputation in the field of business
financial protection healthcare
solutions and
in providing a long-term safe and
effective investment
results here at prudential vietnam
we listen we understand and we take
action
with this brand statement prudential
vietnam
encourages everybody to not only listen
and understand
but to also transform our goals into
action
in order to realize our dreams and
achieve greater things
in life here at prudential vietnam
we are committed to always put our
customers
in the heart of our mission and we wish
to accompany you
in creating a financial freedom and a
solid future in the face of this
constantly changing
world and with that being said we are
cordially inviting you for a free
financial seminar
on march 27 and 28 from 1 to 5
pm at the second floor of loricott's
forwarder office in this
seminar mr trung wong yu the urban
manager of prudential vietnam
will teach you on how you can achieve
financial independence
how to build wealth and invest your
money wisely
while taking care of yourself loved ones
and of the things that truly matters
and since you matter for us here in
prudential vietnam
we don't just want to protect you and
your family but we also want to offer
you
valuable and meaningful gifts and
freebies that you can avail during the
seminar
or when you avail any of our products
should you wish to join a seminar and
avail our exciting freebies
kindly accomplish the google form
through the link attached in this video
and we will see you at glory cuts for
wider office on march 27 and 28
for the free financial seminar brought
to us by prudential vietnam
you